LEANDRO IBARRA

Sr Analyst

- +54 341 3243616
- lea14_9@hotmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/leandro-ibarra/
- github.com/leandroibarra/
- Argentina, SF

EDUCATION

University Systems Analyst Instituto Politécnico Superior 2010 - 2014

KNOWLEDGE AND SKILLS

ActiveCollab, AJAX, Amazon Web Services (AWS), Angular, AngularJS, Apache, API Rest, ASP, Bitbucket, Bootstrap, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Full Stack Development, Web Development, Eloquent, Express.js, Agile project management, Project management, Git, GitHub, Gitlab, HTML, Ionic Framework, JavaScript, JIRA, ¡Query, ¡Query UI, JSON, LAMP, Laravel, LESS, Team leadership, Linux, Lumen, MEAN, Agile methodologies, Microsoft SQL Server, MongoDB, MySQL, NestJS, Node.js, NoSQL, PHP, PhpMyAdmin, PostgreSQL, SASS, Scrum, Slim Framework, SQL, SVN, Tortoise SVN, Trello, TypeScript, Vue.js, WordPress, XAMPP, XML.

PROFILE

Systems Analyst with extensive experience as a Full Stack Developer and Team Leader in different software companies. Solid performance in contact with clients, identifying needs, preparing documentation and solving problems. Self-taught, curious, proactive, with knowledge of agile methodologies. Proven ability to lead teams aimed at generating a collaborative work culture. Mastery of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, AngularJS, Angular, NodeJS, Express, NestJS, PHP, WordPress, Laravel, SQL, SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB, among others.

EXPERIENCE

- O Accenture Argentina October 2024 - Actually Sr Analyst
- Coderio | Software Company January 2024 - October 2024 Backend Developer
 - Development of new features, debugging and bug fixing for e-commerce.
 - Integration with different client systems.
 - Adding configuration features to the administration panel.

Whyline

July 2022 - October 2023

Engineering Manager / Team Leader

- Manage projects with teams of different members and disciplines.
- Guarantee daily status meetings with the teams, as well as weekly progress meetings, task estimation, one-on-one, and performance review.
- Promote a culture of teamwork and a horizontal relationship between peers.
- Collaborate with blockages and ensure progress in each of the projects. Assist new team members with their onboardings.
- Attend technical and status meetings with the client, collect incidents, determine their priorities, and agree on the developments of each deliverable or sprint.
- Carry out the deployments in the different environments (development, testing, production) along with the necessary documentation.

June 2020 - June 2022

Full Stack Developer

- Development of new functionalities in existing systems built on different backend and frontend technologies, as well as debugging and correcting reported errors.
- Integration with external client systems according to their needs.
- Contribute to the definition of tasks as well as to the estimates of effort and technical needs.
- Collaboration in the deployment to different environments: development, integration, production.

Puntoini Software July 2018 - June 2020 Full Stack Developer

- Responsible for the development and maintenance of institutional sites.
- Responsible for the development and implementation of a system for the automation of bank reconciliations for a company dedicated to the commercialization of financial and agricultural products and instruments.
- Review of client requirements and correction of reported errors. Responsible for carrying out demonstrations and collecting feedback from end users.
 Documentation of the necessary tasks of the project and definition of the steps to follow for its development and implementation.
- Responsible for deployments in different environments (development, testing, production) and analysis of usability data.

O Dynamic Mind August 2012 - June 2018 Full Stack Developer

- Development and maintenance of institutional sites.
- Development of Rest API for engagement system to be consumed by frontend systems and mobile applications.
- Development of application for engagement system configuration and its corresponding statistics reporting.
- Active guards required to control and monitor the correct operation of the API and reporting system on days and times of high demand.
- Participation in ceremonies with the team: status meetings, progress and task reviews, estimates, retrospectives, etc.
- Participation in onboardings of new team members.

Oh!STUDIO Soluciones en internet January 2012 - July 2012

Web Developer

- Responsible for the maintenance and development of e-learning platforms.
- Development and maintenance of institutional websites.